hey what's up YouTube it's been a while
I'm back with another video that's going
to help you be able to change your life
and your business and make more money I
want to show you a framework that you
can copy that'll be able to make you
millions and here's the thing is I want
to teach you exactly what I have done
over the last 22 years in my experience
to be able to create millions and tens
of millions of dollars online what works
so that you don't have to take a lot of
time to try to figure it out yourself
and to know exactly what steps to do to
get those results for yourself again for
those you I haven't met yet my name is
Jeremiah Kowski as you can see from the
page here and I've been in the online
marketing space with coaches trainers
mentors seminar leaders back in the day
we sold CD and DVD products to be able
to make tens of millions of dollars
selling those online and that's why I
dedicated my life exclusively to in my
career and that's what I do I work with
hundreds of coaches mentors trainers
speakers authors thought leaders every
single week in my wealthy coach Academy
program and I'd love to see you in there
inside of that program you can go check
out one of the links below to see how to
get access into that and how to jump
into that program with us now what I
want to talk about here is copying
copying is something that we are taught
is a bad thing to do and yes of course
you don't want to plagiarize that's
there's a difference between plagiarism
you don't want to copy what somebody's
actually product is you can get in
trouble for that number one and to be
honest most coaches their products
aren't even that great and so if I
copied other coaches they wouldn't be
that good the reason why my company my
business and our program is so much
better is because of the Blood Sweat and
Tears that I've actually put into the
program to make sure that it gets people
results and I've geared it towards those
who I know I can deliver results to what
they need the step by steps that are
going to get them results and I walk you
through that inside of my wealthy coach
Academy program I'm going to take part
of that program out of it though and
give it to you here for free pro bono
you're not going to have to pay anything
by watching this video right here and so
this might be the number one video that
you watch all year and I'm going to be
recommending this constantly to people
to be watching this this is this is a
huge take right here and so the first
thing is is this though learn to copy
Frameworks success leaves Clues success
leaves Clues as to what works there are
other successful people that are coaches
mentors trainers that are out there that
are marketing successfully they're
getting clients successfully and if you
just do what they did in their marketing
you would also be successful yourself we
have it in our mind so often I got to be
so original this one original first idea
that pops up and while that's a great
thought it makes us feel really good it
doesn't pay the bills the other thing is
this is that originality really doesn't
make as big of a difference until you
hit about $10 million and we've actually
built businesses I I have that have gone
to over $20 million and there's a lot of
originality behind that but we got there
the foundation that we got there in all
of those businesses to get to six
figures and then to seven figures where
most of you are looking to reach in your
business if you're watching this right
now you're probably trying to make at
least six figures you've been trying and
trying you got a great product you got
great information but you're not going
to need kind of clients that you want
people aren't buying from you and so
that's what we're going to be talking
about is what does it take to actually
get people to buy from you copy what
works from other people go out there and
do some Market Research in your market
research I want you to look at the
marketing I want you to look at the
content I want you to look at and when I
talk about content I'm talking about the
topics I'm talking about what is the
surface level like for instance I'm
about to launch a brand new free
training this week we're just buttoning
up a few things on it all about
Instagram ads there are three top
marketers that I have seen that I
respect think are amazing that are
competitors of mine that have launched
very successful Instagram ad funnels
that I've seen and I know and I've done
Facebook ad funnels for a long time but
not necessarily an Instagram ads funnel
so what I did was this now check this
out cuz my Integrity requires me to do
this this I spent 9 months mastering
Instagram ads with multiple clients
multiple budget lots of ways to do it
what not to do and then I made a funnel
that even though I copied the idea that
I saw somebody else did 100% I'm I'm
telling you I did like I like I saw
somebody else they they promoted this
Instagram ads lead magnet I copied them
I make I'm making my own Instagram ads
lead magnet but the content of it what
I'm actually teaching in it is from my
experiences it's from what I've done
it's from what I've tested that I'm
walking people through very simply in it
and it's it's going to be a great class
it's going to be a great training uh if
you're on my email list you're able to
get access to it and check it out um if
you're watching this in the next week or
so there might be a link as well below
this video or we've moved on to another
offer but all that to say I copied the
idea from a proven and I actually saw
multiple people doing a similar offer
and they were all very successful and I
was like okay that's a great hook
Instagram ads of course people want to
know like how do I make Instagram ads
work for me how do I make them produce
the results that I want of course they
want to know that and so but then what I
did was I made my own take my own spin
my own version of that kind of content
and I'll tell you this I actually
actually went through some of the offers
that my competitors had and I'm like
this is all they're teaching this is it
this is like Bare
Bones not actually even gonna help
anybody and I and I actually kind of
chuckled to myself inside because I was
like
okay even like if I teach 10% of what I
know about Instagram ad it's going to be
10 times better than anything else
that's out there which is what I hear
frequently from our clients is they're
like I went through this training for
this person and all that and your stuff
is way better and so with that I was
able to copy a competitor their idea
from their marketing and I know I have
so much confidence it's a proven lead
magnet that's going to work for me my
next lead magnet that I'm going to be
making all about Evergreen marketing I'm
literally going to be looking at who is
teaching Evergreen marketing right now
and copying those funnels exactly in my
own take my own Spin and my own way of
doing this and so we're taught that like
copying what works from other people is
not the right thing to do when in fact
it is the very most right thing to do do
any business owner who is worth their
salt who's making any kind of money has
copied other people in fact this video
right now I'm actually G to give a shout
out on X on formerly known as Twitter
there's a marketer name's I think his
name is Charlie Morgan and I saw he did
a video just like this and I'm like you
know what I'm going to I literally
tweeted back at him I don't know if you
call it X back but I thank you for for
giving me permission to copy your video
idea and I was like I watched this video
I like oh that's great like it it hit me
in my cor like I got to share this with
people and I got to share my experience
of how I've done this in every business
that we've ever built we look at okay
what are the systems what are the
Frameworks what are the ways that the
marketing Works what are the marketing
hooks what is the language by studying
okay they have the same customer as us
let's offer this same exact thing right
here let's let's structure it in a
similar way let's combine these two or
three ideas Frankenstein it together
into something that's 10 times better
and that's exactly how we have built
multiple businesses that have made
Millions problem is people have too much
pride and ego and they've been taught
through traditional education that it's
wrong to do this and there's something
wrong about it that it's cheating
somehow when in fact it's not and then
we have artificial intelligence which
makes it 10 times easier to be able to
get the questions that we want
answered dial in exactly what our
marketing is and often times yes copying
a ideas that have
worked and then we end up feeling like I
meet so many people that they could be
making so much more money but their
arrogance and pride around this thing
right here stops them from doing so and
they call it wisdom or Integrity I'm
sorry but it's not wisdom or Integrity
it's
absolute stupidity it
is and I might might lose some followers
for saying
that but it is the smartest most
effective way of you ever hear about
working smarter not harder this is a
work smarter not harder thing right here
every single company every single
business does
this you
know another great great example back to
like Charlie Morgan's video that he
talked about this uh when vine came out
the little short form videos uh that
then Tik Tok copied that and then
Instagram reels and Snapchat and all
that and it just became so multi-billion
dollar companies same with AI they're
all copying what each other's homework
is that they're
doing and it's not a bad thing because
there's different flavors and different
different types of products for every
single person and so if you want to be
effective in your business the number
one thing that you want to do is you
want to copy
what works you want to
duplicate what works follow the money of
who is successful already and do what
they do now the number one way to be
able to do this is to get a coach or a
mentor who has followed that path for
you now I coach and Mentor a number of
coaches and mentors and so in that this
is exactly what you want to show and
teach to your
clients is that they can be successful
by copying what you've done or what
other people have done that you can
refer to or reference to or share
stories of by connecting with people and
when you can show somebody that you
understand what they're going through in
their own words from their own
perspective in your marketing and you
look at who else out there is doing
that whether it be on Amazon books
whether it be on other people on
Instagram YouTube Facebook and you copy
those
ideas you can be successful by building
out funnels and landing pages and Lead
magnets and getting people on your email
list and the number one thing that you
need to do you need to grow your email
list overall you need to get people on
an email list
that you can Market to consistently to
nurture and build that trust and keep
that connection with people there's a
process that we do to be able to do this
that we walk people through by using
webinars in my wealthy coach Academy
program we walk you through step by step
how we use webinars and Lead magnets to
grow our email list to be able to get
more clients and to close more sales and
to do so Evergreen on autopilot so that
we're not working 10 20 30 hours a week
we're able to even work just five hours
a week or less many weeks and still get
massive results and that's what I I want
to show you inside of my wealthy coach
Academy program I'd love to see you in
there all right we'll talk soon
everybody have a good one